Guide to the Office of the President Records, Virginia B. Smith Files, 1950-2010 (bulk 1977-1986)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Series III. Alumnae/i
  - Princeton Vassar Club, 1979 (Folder 10.41)
  - Rochester Vassar Club, 1981-1983 (Folder 10.42)
  - AAVC — Elizabeth Schalk, 1978-1980 (Folder 10.43)
  - AAVC Calendar, 1981-1982, 1983-1984 (Folder 10.44)
  - AAVC Biographers’ Banquet, Apr 30, 1981 (Folder 10.45)
  - Alumnae/i Admission Workshop, 1980-1981 (Folder 10.46)
  - Alumni Admission Workshop, Sep 1980 (Folder 10.47)
  - Daughters and Sons of Vassar — Alumnae/i, 1979-1983 (Folder 10.48)
  - AAVC Fall Council, 1980-1981 (Folder 10.49)
  - AAVC Fall Council, Oct 1979 (Folder 11.1)
  - AAVC Fall Council, Oct 1978 (Folder 11.2)
  - Alumni Workshop (Confidential), Sep 1981 (Folder 11.3)
  - AAVC — Special Meeting, Oct 1980 (Folder 11.4)
  - Biographer’s Art — Seminar, Apr – May 1981 (Folder 11.5)
  - Vassar Reunion Handbook, 1980 (Folder 11.6)
  - V.C. Reunions, 1986 (Folder 11.7)
  - Reunion, 1986 (Folder 11.8)
  - Reunion Weekend, 1985 (Folder 11.9)
  - Reunion, 1985 (Folder 11.10)
  - Class of ’35 — Gala Dinner, Jun 7, 1985 (Folder 11.11)
  - Reunion, 1984-1985 (Folder 11.12)
  - Reunion, 1984 (Folder 11.13)
  - Reunion, 1982 (Folder 11.14)
  - Reunions, 1982-1983 (Folder 11.15)
  - Reunion, 1983 (Folder 11.16)
  - Reunion 1984 — (Class of 1934) (Folder 11.17)
  - Vassar Reunions, 1981 (Folder 11.18)
  - Reunions, 1979-1980 (Folder 11.19)
  - Reunion — Annual Meeting, 1980 (Folder 11.20)
  - Alumnae/i Reunions, 1978 (Folder 11.21)
  - Alumnae/i Reunions, 1977-1978 (Folder 11.22)
  - Alumnae Reunions, 1976-1977 (Folder 11.23)
  - Alumnae Reunions, 1976 (Folder 11.24)
  - AAVC — Santa Barbara Seminar, 1979 (Folder 11.25)
  - Class of 1912, 1979-1983 (Folder 11.26)
  - Class of 1912 70th Reunion, Apr 1982 (Folder 11.27)
  - Class of 1913, 1977 (Folder 11.28)
  - Class of 1914, 1980 (Folder 11.29)
  - Class of 1917 and 1918 Informal Reunion, Oct 15, 1980 (Folder 11.30)
  - Dinner with Class of 1921, Apr 28, 1982 (Folder 11.31)
  - Class of 1920 Dinner, Apr 25, 1980 (Folder 11.32)
  - Class of 1922, 1981 (Folder 11.33)
  - Class of 1926 Lunch, Oct 26 (Folder 11.34)
  - Class of 1927 Dinner, Sep 19, 1979 (Folder 11.35)
  - Class of 1928, Apr 1978 (Folder 11.36)
  - Class of 1930 Informal Reunion, 1982 (Folder 11.37)
  - Class of 1931 Dinner, Sep 21, 1979 (Folder 11.38)
  - Class of 1932 mini Reunion, 1980 (Folder 11.39)
  - Class of 1935 Dinner, Nov 7, 1979 (Folder 11.40)
  - Class of 1935 Study, 1977-1979 (Folder 11.41)
  - Class of 1937, 1981 (Folder 11.42)
  - Dinner with Class of 1953 — Informal Reunion, Sep 24, 1981 (Folder 11.43)
- Series IV. Within the College
  - Art and Gallery 78-79 Annual Report, 1979 (Folder 12.1)
  - Art Gallery 83-84 Annual Report, 1984 (Folder 12.2)
  - Annual Reports — Academic, 1977-1978 (Folder 12.3)
  - Annual Reports — Administrative, 1977-1978 (Folder 12.4)
  - Annual Reports — Dean of Faculty Reports, 1977-1978 (Folder 12.5)
  - Annual Reports — Programs and Committees, 1977-1978 (Folder 12.6)
  - Annual Reports, 1977-1978 (Folder 12.7)
  - Annual Reports — Dean of Faculty Reports, 1977-1978 (Folder 12.8)
  - Master Lists, 1978-1979 (Folder 12.9)
  - Annual Reports — Academic Departments, 1978-1979 (Folder 12.10)
  - Annual Reports — Administrative, 1978-1979 (Folder 12.11)
  - Annual Reports — Programs and Committees, 1978-1979 (Folder 12.12)
  - Annual Reports — Student Affairs Reports, 1978-1979 (Folder 12.13)
  - General Reports, 1978-1979 (Folder 12.14)
  - Annual Report to the President, 1978-1979 (Folder 12.15)
  - Annual Reports, 1978-1979 (Folder 12.16)
  - Annual Reports, 1978-1979 (Folder 12.17)
  - Annual Reports — Dean of the Faculty, 1978-1979 (Folder 12.18)
  - Annual Reports — Dean of the Faculty, 1978-1979 (Folder 12.19)
  - Annual Reports — Student Affairs Reports, 1979-1980 (Folder 12.20)
  - Annual Reports — Dean of the College, 1979-1980 (Folder 12.21)
  - Annual Reports — Student Services Reports, 1980-1981 (Folder 12.22)
  - Annual Reports — Dean of the College, 1980-1981 (Folder 13.1)
  - Annual Reports — Departmental, 1980-1981 (Folder 13.2)
  - Annual Reports — Various, 1980-1981 (Folder 13.3)
  - Annual Reports — Dean of the College, 1981-1982 (Folder 13.4)
  - Annual Reports — Departmental, 1981-1982 (Folder 13.5)
  - Annual Reports — Career Development and Field Work, 1981-1982 (Folder 13.6)
  - Annual Reports — Dean of the College, 1982-1983 (Folder 13.7)
  - Annual Reports — Departmental, 1982-1983 (Folder 13.8)
  - Annual Reports — Departmental I, 1983-1984 (Folder 13.9)
  - Annual Reports — Departmental II, 1983-1984 (Folder 13.10)
  - Gifts to Vassar, 1984 (Folder 13.11)
  - Annual Reports — Art Gallery, 1983-1984 (Folder 14.1)
  - Annual Reports, 1983-1984 (Folder 14.2)
  - Annual Reports — Various, 1982-1985 (Folder 14.3)
  - Gifts — Miscellaneous and Anonymous, 1974-1979 (Folder 14.4)
  - President’s Funds and Gifts, 1979 (Folder 14.5)
  - Sarah Gibson Blanding Fund/Chair — Class of 1919, 1974-1979 (Folder 14.6)
  - Blegen Fund, 1978-1980 (Folder 14.7)
  - Jane Breckir Scholarship Fund, 1975-1976 (Folder 14.8)
  - Agnes Rindge Claflin Memorial, 1977-1979 (Folder 14.9)
  - Connor, Ralph Mr. and Mrs., 1964-1981 (Folder 14.10)
  - Dickinson-Kayden Fund, 1976-1981 (Folder 14.11)
  - Dickinson-Kayden Lecture (Budget Folder), 1976-1981 (Folder 14.12)
  - Mr. and Mrs. William Clay Ford, 1973-1977 (Folder 14.13)
  - Friends of Vassar — 1975, 1974 (Folder 14.14)
  - Gertrude G. Garnsey Fund, 1974-1978 (Folder 14.15)
  - General Electric Education and Charitable Fund, 1974-1979 (Folder 14.16)
  - Goodbody Fund (Marv B. and Harold P.), 1980-1981 (Folder 14.17)
  - Graduate Work Proposals, 1979 (Folder 14.18)
  - Hirschhorn Gift, 1978 (Folder 14.19)
  - Huber Family (J.M. Huber Corp) and Family Contributions, 1973-1981 (Folder 14.20)
  - Molly Thacher Kazan Fund, 1972 (Folder 14.21)
  - International Business Machines, 1977-1981 (Folder 14.22)
  - William R. Kenan, Jr. Charitable Trust, 1976-1981 (Folder 14.23)
  - Koldyke, Martin, 1976-1978 (Folder 14.24)
  - Louise Boyd Lichtenstein Dale Chair in Modern Languages, 1974-1977 (Folder 14.25)
  - Rebecca Lowrie’s Gift, 1974-1980 (Folder 14.26)
  - Maguire Fellowships, 1974-1980 (Folder 14.27)
  - Noyes Family, 1974-1977 (Folder 14.28)
  - Mr. and Mrs. George O’Neill, 1978 (Folder 14.29)
  - Parents and Friends of Vassar, 1978 (Folder 14.30)
  - Francis F. Randolph Rare Book Room, 1975-1977 (Folder 14.31)
  - Sarah Tod Fitz Randolph Scholarship and Salary Fund, 1974-1979 (Folder 14.32)
  - Lucy Maynard Salmon Chair of American History, 1973-1977 (Folder 14.33)
  - Summerfield Scholarship Fund (Solon E. Summerfield Foundation), 1975 (Folder 14.34)
  - Dorothy Linder Silberberg Scholarship Fund, 1972-1977 (Folder 14.35)
  - C. Mildred Thompson Scholarship Fund, 1975-1977 (Folder 14.36)
  - Potential Donors (A-L), 1974-1981 (Folder 14.37)
  - Potential Donors (M-Z), 1974-1979 (Folder 14.38)
  - Class of 1975 Fund, 1974 (Folder 14.39)
  - Class of 1976 Fund, 1975 (Folder 14.40)
  - Class of 1977 Fund, 1976 (Folder 14.41)
  - Grants — I (Folder 14.42)
  - Grants — II (Folder 14.43)
  - Grants — III (Folder 14.44)
  - Rejected Grants (Folder 14.45)
  - Miscellaneous Grant Information, 1977-1981 (Folder 15.1)
  - National Heritage Trust Grant, 1980 (Folder 15.2)
  - Foundations — General, 1979 (Folder 15.3)
  - Foundations — General, 1977-1979 (Folder 15.4)
  - Compton Foundation, 1980 (Folder 15.5)
  - Danforth Foundation, 1979-1980 (Folder 15.6)
  - Danforth Foundation, 1971-1979 (Folder 15.7)
  - Arthur Vining Davis Foundation, 1973-1977 (Folder 15.8)
  - Dreyfus Foundation, Inc. (Camille and Henry), 1979-1980 (Folder 15.9)
  - Exxon Education Foundation, 1979-1983 (Folder 15.10)
  - Exxon Education Foundation, 1976-1978 (Folder 15.11)
  - Booth Ferris Foundation, 1978-1980 (Folder 15.12)
  - Mudd, Seeley G., Foundation, 1980-1981 (Folder 15.13)
  - National Science Foundation, 1976-1980 (Folder 15.14)
  - New York Times Foundation, 1979-1981 (Folder 15.15)
  - Parents and Friends of Vassar College, 1974-1978 (Folder 15.16)
  - Presser Foundation, 1974-1978 (Folder 15.17)
  - Sloan Foundation, 1972-1978 (Folder 15.18)
  - The Rockefeller Foundation, 1979 (Folder 15.19)
  - Shell Companies Foundation, 1974-1979 (Folder 15.20)
  - Russell Sage Foundation, 1974-1976 (Folder 15.21)
  - Woodrow Wilson Fellowship Foundation, 1972-1980 (Folder 15.22)
  - Ford Foundation, 1979-1981 (Folder 15.23)
  - Ford Foundation, 1971-1976 (Folder 15.24)
  - Hewlett Foundation, 1978-1980 (Folder 15.25)
  - Kellogg Foundation, 1977-1979 (Folder 15.26)
  - Kresge Foundation, 1974-1977 (Folder 15.27)
  - The Henry Luce Foundation, Inc., 1973-1979 (Folder 15.28)
  - McCann Foundation, 1975-1978 (Folder 15.29)
  - Daniel J. Mahoney, Jr. Trust, 1975-1978 (Folder 15.30)
  - “Prorject ‘80” — Report of Gifts, 1979-1980 (Folder 15.31)
  - Charles E. Merrill Trust, 1976-1979 (Folder 15.32)
  - Kresge Foundation, 1980-1983 (Folder 15.33)
  - The Henry Luce Foundation, 1980-1981 (Folder 15.34)
  - McCann Foundation, 1979 (Folder 15.35)
  - A.A.V.C Budget, 1980-1983 (Folder 15.36)
  - ACUSNY Paper, 1982 (Folder 15.37)
  - Administrative Personnel Restructuring, 1982 (Folder 15.38)
  - Admission of Foreign Students, 1980 (Folder 15.39)
  - Affirmative Action, 1979 (Folder 15.40)
  - Antolini House, 1981 (Folder 15.41)
  - Astin Study/Change Magazine, 1981-1982 (Folder 15.42)
  - American Bar Association’s College and University Program Advisory Commission, 1984-1985 (Folder 15.43)
  - ABA’s National Conference on Law in Undergraduate Liberal Education, Mar 1985 (Folder 15.44)
  - American Culture, 1982 (Folder 15.45)
  - Benefit Plans, 1980-1981 (Folder 15.46)
  - Dorothy Berry, 1982-1984 (Folder 15.47)
  - Christina Biaggi, 1986 (Folder 15.48)
  - Lisa Birnbach College/Guide Books, 1984 (Folder 15.49)
  - Blegen Fund, 1979-1981 (Folder 15.50)
  - Black Caucus, 1983-1985 (Folder 15.51)
  - David Black, 1985 (Folder 15.52)
  - Maxwell Brace House, 1980 (Folder 15.53)
  - Bridge vs. Vassar, 1982 (Folder 15.54)
  - Brooks Admission Survey, 1983 (Folder 15.55)
  - T. Butler, 1984 (Folder 15.56)
  - Cambridge Report, 1982-1983 (Folder 15.57)
  - Cambridge Report “Comments”, 1982-1983 (Folder 15.58)
  - Campus Cheating (Confidential), 1982-1983 (Folder 15.59)
  - Campus Vehicles, 1980 (Folder 15.60)
  - Career Development and Field Work, 1980-1983 (Folder 15.61)
  - Carey Estate, 1981-1982 (Folder 15.62)
  - Carswell, Dorothy (Confidential), 1981 (Folder 15.63)
  - Central Hudson Proposal, 1981 (Folder 15.64)
  - Central Steno, 1979-1980 (Folder 15.65)
  - CEO List, 1983 (Folder 15.66)
  - Yu Shanrui/Hebei University, 1984-1985 (Folder 15.67)
  - Chinese/American Education Exchange, 1984-1985 (Folder 15.68)
  - Tucker/China, 1984-1985 (Folder 15.69)
  - Chemistry Building, 1981-1984 (Folder 15.70)
  - Chemistry Building — Architect’s Supplemental Information, 1981 (Folder 15.71)
  - Co-Educational Housing, 1983 (Folder 15.72)
  - Coeducation at Lathrop House, 1983 (Folder 15.73)
  - College Council, 1983 (Folder 15.74)
  - College Professor, 1982 (Folder 15.75)
  - College/High School, 1982 (Folder 15.76)
  - College Owned Houses, 1980 (Folder 15.77)
  - Committee Structure, 1980 (Folder 15.78)
  - Committee on Curricular Policies, 1982 (Folder 15.79)
  - Comparative Enrollment Information, 1981 (Folder 15.80)
  - Comparative Fringe Information, 1980 (Folder 15.81)
  - Compensation and Benefits Survey of College and University Chief Executive Officers, 1983-1984 (Folder 15.82)
  - Computer Acquisition/Projects, 1982-1983 (Folder 15.83)
  - Computer Literacy/Faculty-Staff, 1981 (Folder 15.84)
  - Dyson Family Scholarship, 1983 (Folder 15.85)
  - Consortium on Financing Higher Education (COFHE), 1981 (Folder 15.86)
  - Consultants, 1983-1986 (Folder 15.87)
  - Special Convocation — Conflict and Peace, 1982 (Folder 15.88)
  - Corporate Connection, 1982 (Folder 15.89)
  - Chaplaincy — Mrs. Catlin, 1979-1981 (Folder 16.1)
  - Chaplaincy Research, 1982 (Folder 16.2)
  - Chaplaincy — Original Responses to Review Recommendations, 1980-1982 (Folder 16.3)
  - Chaplaincy — Supplemental Materials Given to VBS, 1979-1981 (Folder 16.4)
  - Chaplaincy, 1980-1981 (Folder 16.5)
  - Smith Statement of Review of Chaplaincy, 1979 (Folder 16.6)
  - Religion Department, 1976-1984 (Folder 16.7)
  - Chaplaincy Review Committee Report, Oct 1980 (Folder 16.8)
  - Bruce A. Kimball — Interview for Chaplaincy Position, May 1981 (Folder 16.9)
  - Chaplaincy Position — Interview of Howard Berman, Apr 1981 (Folder 16.10)
  - Board of Trustee By-Laws (Folder 16.11)
  - Deaccessioning Policy, 1980 (Folder 16.12)
  - Dean of Studies Office, 1982 (Folder 16.13)
  - Faculty Salary Budget, 1979-1980 (Folder 16.14)
  - Defense Advisory Committee on Women in the Services (DACOWITS), 1980-1981 (Folder 16.15)
  - Executive Director of Development Position, 1984 (Folder 16.16)
  - Development Program, 1981 (Folder 16.17)
  - Development/Alumnae Computer Project, 1980 (Folder 16.18)
  - Development Policy Committee, 1979-1980 (Folder 16.19)
  - Development Regional Files, 1980-1982 (Folder 16.20)
  - Development Consultants, 1984 (Folder 16.21)
  - Development Strategy and Solicitation Sub-Committee, 1983 (Folder 16.22)
  - Diagnostic Tests, 1984 (Folder 16.23)
  - Diversity, 1982 (Folder 16.24)
  - William F. Dorrill, 1981 (Folder 16.25)
  - Drivers, 1980-1982 (Folder 16.26)
  - Efficiency, 1982 (Folder 16.27)
  - Essex House, 1980 (Folder 16.28)
  - Everywoman’s Guide, 1981 (Folder 16.29)
  - Edelson, Maurice, 1983 (Folder 16.30)
  - Energy, 1981-1984; (1 folder) (Folder 16.31)
  - Foreign Language, 1981-1984 (Folder 16.32)
  - Foundations, 1980 (Folder 16.33)
  - FPCC — Athletics, 1980 (Folder 16.34)
  - FRAS (Federal Resources Advisory Service), 1981 (Folder 16.35)
  - 1982-1983 Fee Schedule (Folder 16.36)
  - Faculty Applicants, 1983 (Folder 16.37)
  - Confidentiality of Faculty Records, 1980 (Folder 16.38)
  - FASC, 1981-1983 (Folder 16.39)
  - Federal Grants, 1980 (Folder 16.40)
  - Feminist Press Advisory Board, 1980 (Folder 16.41)
  - Financial Planning, Jun 30, 1980 (Folder 16.42)
  - Faculty, 1983-1985 (Folder 16.43)
  - FASC Materials, 1983-1984 (Folder 16.44)
  - Workshop of the new FPCC, 1984 (Folder 16.45)
  - FCC, 1981-1984 (Folder 16.46)
  - FPCC, 1980-1983 (Folder 16.47)
  - Family Institute, 1981 (Folder 16.48)
  - Gannett Proposal, 1980 (Folder 16.49)
  - Gay People’s Alliance, 1982-1983 (Folder 16.50)
  - GTE Proposal, 1982 (Folder 16.51)
  - Rev. Judy Gourley, 1985 (Folder 16.52)
  - Hadley, 1980-1981 (Folder 16.53)
  - Harvard Black Rock Forest, 1982-1983 (Folder 16.54)
  - Health Benefit Plan Changes, 1980 (Folder 16.55)
  - Health Personnel, 1982 (Folder 16.56)
  - Health Services, 1982 (Folder 16.57)
  - Health Care Plan Cost (Medical Insurance), 1980-1983 (Folder 16.58)
  - Humanities Center, 1980-1981 (Folder 16.59)
  - Human Renewal, Inc., 1978 (Folder 16.60,)
  - Human Relations Resources, 1979 (Folder 16.61)
  - M.C. Hyde, 1983-1984 (Folder 16.62)
  - Hudson Valley Chamber Orchestra, 1984-1985 (Folder 16.63)
  - IBM Superintendents Workshop (Folder 16.64)
  - Williamson, E. (Mrs. Gregory Williamson), 1980-1984 (Folder 16.65)
  - IBM Grant Discussion Paper, 1983 (Folder 16.67)
  - Independent Higher Education, 1981 (Folder 16.68)
  - Interdisciplinary Activities, 1981 (Folder 16.69)
  - International Concerns, 1979-1982 (Folder 16.70)
  - Investment Gift Funds, 1980-1981 (Folder 16.71)
  - Jewish Studies, 1984 (Folder 16.72)
  - Lobbying, 1982 (Folder 16.73)
  - Luncheon Meeting with M. Shanley (and B. Darlington), 1979-1981 (Folder 16.74)
  - MacArthur Foundation, 1984 (Folder 16.75)
  - Major Gifts, 1982 (Folder 16.76)
  - Maintenance, 1979 (Folder 16.77)
  - Management Salaries, 1978-1979 (Folder 16.78)
  - Marine Midland Bank/Industrial Valley Bank, 1981 (Folder 16.79)
  - Maxted, 1985-1986 (Folder 16.80)
  - Medical Services Proposal, 1979-1982 (Folder 16.81)
  - Middaugh, Dr. Michael F., 1980 (Folder 16.82)
  - Minority Student Roster, 1983-1984 (Folder 16.83)
  - Merit Awards, 1983 (Folder 16.84)
  - Selective Service Compliance, 1984; (3 folders) (Folder 17.1)
  - Modern Language Association of America Advisory Board, 1980 (Folder 17.2)
  - MacNeil/Lehrer Correspondence, 1984 (Folder 17.3)
  - Named Chairs, 1981 (Folder 17.4)
  - Natural Heritage Trust Grants, 1980 (Folder 17.5)
  - NEH Career Grant Proposal, 1982-1983 (Folder 17.6)
  - Nepotism, 1982 (Folder 17.7)
  - Nuclear Armament, 1983-1984 (Folder 17.8)
  - Officers Staff Meeting, 1983 (Folder 17.9)
  - Oral History (Folder 17.10)
  - Overview Final Report, 1980 (Folder 17.11)
  - Pappas, Irene/Drama, 1979-1980 (Folder 17.12)
  - Personnel Matters, 1982-1984 (Folder 17.13)
  - Priorities, 1979-1981 (Folder 17.14)
  - Professor X, 1983 (Folder 17.15)
  - Professional Class, 1980 (Folder 17.16)
  - Randolph Book Collection, 1983 (Folder 17.17)
  - Ad Hoc Committee for Special Recruiting — Board of Trustees, 1981 (Folder 17.18)
  - Richter Memorial Fund, 1984 (Folder 17.19)
  - Research Resources Library, 1981 (Folder 17.20)
  - Inez Ryberg, 1981 (Folder 17.21)
  - Salary Complaints, 1984 (Folder 17.22)
  - Scholarship, 1980 (Folder 17.23)
  - Student Aid Stories, 1981 (Folder 17.24)
  - Slide Show, 1983 (Folder 17.25)
  - Student Recruitment Show, 1983 (Folder 17.26)
  - Summer Career Opportunity Institute, 1984 (Folder 17.27)
  - Summer Theater Institute, 1982-1983 (Folder 17.28)
  - TIRC, 1981 (Folder 17.29)
  - Robin Trainor, 1982-1983 (Folder 17.30)
  - “Unscrewed”, 1982-1983 (Folder 17.31)
  - Unisex Pension Tables, 1981 (Folder 17.32)
  - Unemployment Insurance, 1980-1982 (Folder 17.33)
  - Union Matters, 1982-1983 (Folder 17.34)
  - Vacancies, 1984 (Folder 17.35)
  - Matthew Vassar’s Monument, 1984 (Folder 17.36)
  - Vassar Advisory Council (and Planning), 1983 (Folder 17.37)
  - Jean Webster Chair, 1981 (Folder 17.38)
  - Weinberg, Sue, 1984 (Folder 17.39)
  - Women in Business, 1981 (Folder 17.40)
  - Budget for the Year 1980-1981, Jan 9, 1981 (Folder 17.41)
  - A — General, 1979-1980 (Folder 17.42)
  - Mackenzie, Marla — Assistant to the President — Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Folder 17.43)
  - Office of Administrative and Student Services (Including Ritterskamp, ’80), 1980-1981 (Folder 17.44)
  - Buckley Amendment (Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act) of 1974), 1975-1978 (Folder 17.45)
  - General Budget, 1979 (Folder 17.46)
  - Administrative Budget Committee/Faculty Student Budget Review Committee, 1978-1980 (Folder 17.47)
  - Auditor’s Report — Peat, Marwick, Mitchell and Co., Jun 30, 1979 (Folder 17.48)
  - Auditor’s Report — Peat, Marwick, Mitchell and Co., Jun 30, 1978 (Folder 17.49)
  - Auditors Report, 1978-1979 (Folder 17.50)
  - Auditor’s Report — Peat, Marwick, Mitchell and Co., Jun 30, 1977 (Folder 17.51)
  - Budget Estimates, 1978-1980 (Folder 17.52)
  - Director of the Budget — Position, 1980 (Folder 17.53)
  - Applications for Director of Budget, 1980 (Folder 17.54)
  - Director of Budget Acknowledgements, 1980 (Folder 17.55)
  - President’s Office Budget Request, 1978-1979 (Folder 17.56)
  - Long Range Planning — Budget, 1976 (Folder 17.57)
  - Expenditures, 1979-1980 (Folder 17.58)
  - Comptroller’s Report to Budget Committee, 1977-1978 (Folder 17.59)
  - Long Range Budget Planning — Library Resources, 1979 (Folder 17.60)
  - Budget/Contingency Funds, 1980 (Folder 17.61)
  - Budget/Contingency Funds, 1978-1979 (Folder 17.62)
  - Budget — Correspondence, 1978-1980 (Folder 17.63)
  - Administrative Budget Committee/Faculty Student Budget Review Committee, 1976-1977 (Folder 17.64)
  - Budget Preparation, 1977-1979 (Folder 17.65)
  - Budget Preparation, 1975-1978 (Folder 17.66)
  - Comptroller’s Reports to the Vice President, 1978-1979 (Folder 18.1)
  - Office of Public Relations — Administrative Director Mary J. Gilbert, 1975-1977 (Folder 18.2)
  - Seven College Study, 1984 (Folder 18.3)
  - Seven College Study of Medical Careers — Budget, 1981 (Folder 18.4)
  - Macy Seven College Study, 1980-1982 (Folder 18.5)
  - Macy Conference, Jun 1980 (Folder 18.6)
  - Macy, Jr. Foundation, Josiah, 1979-1982 (Folder 18.7)
  - Macy, Jr. Foundation, Josiah, 1977-1979 (Folder 18.8)
  - NAICU — National Association of Independent Colleges and Universities, 1979-1988 (Folder 18.9)
  - National Association of Independent Colleges and Universities, 1978-1985 (Folder 18.10)
  - NCHEMS, 1985 (Folder 18.11)
  - NCHEMS/Kellogg Student Outcomes, Jan 1982 (Folder 18.12)
  - National Manpower Institute, 1979-1980 (Folder 18.13)
  - Seven College/Exxon, 1980 (Folder 18.14)
  - Seven College Conference (Radcliffe College), 1980 (Folder 18.15)
  - Seven College Dinner, 1980 (Folder 18.16)
  - Seven College Conference/Macy, 1980-1981 (Folder 18.17)
  - Seven College Conference, 1978-1980 (Folder 18.18)
  - Seven College Conference — Fall, Nov 1981 (Folder 18.19)
  - State Education Department — Organizational and Functional Index, 1980 (Folder 18.20)
  - Hong Kong Vassar Club, Apr 5, 1986 (Folder 18.21)
  - Meeting with Natalie Marshall re: Alumnae House, Jun 12, 1985 (Folder 18.22)
  - Fund Reunion Workshop — Cocktails, 1984 (Folder 18.23)
  - Annual Fund Workshop, Apr 1985 (Folder 18.24)
  - AAVC — General, 1977-1987 (Folder 18.25)
  - AAVC Fund, 1980-1984 (Folder 18.26)
  - AAVC Fund Workshop, 1980-1981 (Folder 18.27)
  - AAVC Fund Workshop, 1977-1980 (Folder 18.28)
  - AAVC Fund Newsletter, 1977-1983 (Folder 18.29)
  - AAVC Board of Directors, 1976-1981 (Folder 18.30)
  - Alumnae House, 1978-1982 (Folder 18.31)
  - Kuhn, Polly M. — AAVC Executive Director, 1981-1982 (Folder 18.32)
  - Polly M. Kuhn, 1983-1984 (Folder 18.33)
  - AAVC — Mary Gesek, 1978-1986 (Folder 18.34)
  - Gillotti, Susan, 1977-1980 (Folder 18.35)
  - AAVC — Kathleen Holman Langan, 1978-1984 (Folder 18.36)
  - Grant Proposals, 1979-1981 (Folder 19.1)
  - Greenwood Grant Proposal (Confidential), 1979 (Folder 19.2)
  - FIPSE — Comprehensive Program, 1981 (Folder 19.3)
  - Grant Proposals (Confidential), 1980-1981 (Folder 19.4)
  - Master Copy of Mass Produced Letters, Statements, Articles, etc., 1979 (Folder 19.5)
  - Self-Study Committee, Vassar — Middle States Team, 1978-1979 (Folder 19.6)
  - Middle States — Self-Study, 1979 (Folder 19.7)
  - Middle States Association of Colleges and Schools (Commission on Higher Education — Annual Institutional Data Summary), 1978-1979 (Folder 19.8)
  - Middle States Association of Colleges and Schools, 1978-1979 (Folder 19.9)
  - Accreditation Visit — Topics for Evaluation, 1978 (Folder 19.10)
  - Self-Study — Extra Copies, 1978 (Folder 19.11)
  - New York State Education Department — New Degree Programs, 1979-1981 (Folder 19.12)
  - New York State Education Department — News Releases, 1978-1981 (Folder 19.13)
  - New York State Education Department — General, 1978-1979 (Folder 19.14)
  - New York State Education Department — The 1978 Progress Report, 1977-1979 (Folder 19.15)
  - New York State Education Department — Heds/Hegis Forms, 1978 (Folder 19.16)
  - Armstrong, James I. Jr. — Music Department, 1981 (Folder 19.17)
  - Asprey, Winifred, 1980 (Folder 19.18)
  - Bean, Joel Jay — Psychology, 1981 (Folder 19.19)
  - Bergon, Frank — English Department, 1981 (Folder 19.20)
  - Cao, Antonio F., 1980 (Folder 19.21)
  - Darlington, Beth — Associate Professor of English, 1981 (Folder 19.22)
  - Ferdinand, 1980 (Folder 19.23)
  - Herbst, Lawrence A. and Clyde Griffen, 1979-1980 (Folder 19.24)
  - Jarsulic, Marc, 1980 (Folder 19.25)
  - Johnson, Kenneth — Geography Department, 1981 (Folder 19.26)
  - Kapschutschenko, Ludmila — Hispanic Department, 1981 (Folder 19.27)
  - Mucci, Joseph F. — Department of Chemistry, 1981 (Folder 19.28)
  - Suter, Robert B., 1980 (Folder 19.29)